Pinelands Folklife Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Field documentation arranged by fieldworker, Field photography descriptions are copied directly from B and C logs via Optical Character Recognition, so errors and abbreviations exist.
  - Jens Lund
    - Field photography on color slide film
      - Sand mining, Bricksboro, New Jersey, September 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-008; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-008; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Sand mining G-Bricksboro; 38GT operation at Whitehead Brothers sand mine, Bricksboro; 1, Sign on road; 2-3, Garage, shop, and office; 4, Screener; 5, Dump truck and front loader at screening area; 6-8, Ed Brown operating front loader; 9-11, Chester "Chet" Rilman operating dump truck; 9-10, Dump truck is being loaded by the screener; 12, Carl Beagle, plant manager; 13, I., Sand piles; r., drier; 14-15, Sand piles, ready for shipment; 16, Interior of loading area of screener; 17-19, Screener; 20, Front loader bringing sand to screener
      - Sand mining, Bricksboro, New Jersey, September 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-009; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-009; 9 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Sand mining G-Bricksboro; 38GT operation at Whitehead Brothers sand mine; 1, Front loader dumping sand into screener; 2, Drier; 3-6, Foundry sand pits, i.e., where foundry sand is dug; 8-9, Thermal sand pits
      - Sign announcing "stock outboard" boat races, Laurel Lake, New Jersey; Yard-ornaments, Heislerville Community Hall; Pole bean field; Grotto shrine, Heislerville, New Jersey, September 19, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-010; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-010; 10 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, Sign announcing "stock outboard" boat races on G-Laurel Lake; 38GT; 2-4, Yard-ornaments near G-Heislerville; 38GT; 5-6, G-Heislerville; 38GT Community Hall, with sign announcing weekly bingo for Heislerville Volunteer Fire Co.; 7-8, Pole bean G-Heislerville; 38GT field; 9-10, Grotto shrine belonging to Hispanic family near G-Heislerville; 38GT
      - Visit to Ted and Jane VonBosse, Port Republic, New Jersey, September 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-011; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-011; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Signs, house, and yard decorations of Ted & Jane VonBosse, at their home on Nacote Creek, near G-Port Republic; 13GT; 1-4, Signs offering decoys and woodcarvings for sale; 5-11, Front of house; 7-11, Driftwood & other decorations on front of house; 11, Terrapin and box turtle shells used as decorations on front of house; 12-15, Whirligig and yard decorations; 16-17, Roughed out decoy used as a yard decoration; 18, Birdhouses and whirligig; 19, Geraniums in old pottery used as yard decorations; 20, 2-dimensional owl figure used to scare birds to keep them from flying into windows
      - Visit to home of Ted and Jane VonBosse, Port Republic, New Jersey, September 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-012; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-012; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Home of Jane & Ted VonBosse, decoy and woodcarvers G-Port Republic; 13GT, on Nacote Creek, Port Republic; 1, House sign and roughed out decoy used as an exterior decoratioa; 2-3, Minnow box used as an exterior decoration; 4-5, Ted VonBosse and unpainted decoys; 6-7, Carved birds by Jane V. and decoys by Ted V.; 8-11, Carved birds and carved human figures by J.V., and decoys by T.V.; 12, Carved birds and miniature boat by J.V.; decoys by T.V.; 13, Decoys by T.V.; carved dog and wooden eggs by J.V.; 15-17, Ted VonBosse in his decoy carving workshop; 18, Lumber pieces and unfinished decoys in Ted VonBosse's decoy carving workshop; 20, Jane VonBosse carving wooden bird in her work area at the VonBosse' s house.
      - Visit to home of Ted and Jane VonBosse, Nacote Creek, Port Republic, New Jersey, September 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-013; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-013; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1, Eel spear made by Martin DeAngelis of Atlantic City, belonging to VonBosses. G-Nacote Creek; 13GT; 2-20, Boats tied up or out of water at G-Nacote Creek Harbor; 13GT on Ted & Jane VonBosse's property; 3-4, Garvey; 5-6, Skiff; 7-9, Sneakbox; 10-12, Sneakbox (below) and pond-box (below); 13-14, Aluminum boat camouflaged for waterfowl hunting; 15-16, Elaborate skiff found and restored by Ted VonB.; 17-18, Sneakbox made by Sam Hunt; 19, Garvey; 20, Live-box for crabs
      - Visit to dock where oyster boats land, Oyster Creek, near Leeds Point, New Jersey, September 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-014; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-014; 7 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-7, Oyster boats tied up at the dock on G-Oyster Creek 09GT, near Leeds Point; 1, Oyster boat "Capt. Curtis Maxwell," belonging to Don Maxwell, Oyster Creek oysterman; 2-5, Oyster dredge and oyster shells aboard the oyster boat "Capt. Curtis Maxwell"; 6, Oyster boat, "Capt. Curtis Maxwell"; 7, Fiberglass ( left) and plywood (right) garveys. The plywood garvey is used for oystering
      - Weekly Saturday night auction, called "the Tabernacle Auction," held at E. H. Harker & Sons auction barn near Tabernacle, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-015; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-015; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Tabernacle; 25GT; 1-20, Saturday night auction, called "the Tabernacle Auction held at E.H. Harker & Sons auction barn near Tabernacle; 1-2, Exterior views of auction barn; 3-4, Retailing produce outside the auction barn; 5, Exterior view of the auction barn, at sunset; 6, Bales of hay awaiting sale; 7, Piglets awaiting sale; 8-19, Panoramas of interior of auction barn while auction is in progress. On the podium are Ronny Harker, auctioneer (holding mike &/or gavel); Nancy Stanley, clerk; Anthony Sparta (wearing billed cap), and other unnamed individuals
      - Weekly Saturday night auction, called "the Tabernacle Auction," held at E. H. Harker & Sons auction barn near Tabernacle, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-016; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-016; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Tabernacle; 25GT; 1-20, Various interior views of auction in progress inside auction barn; 1, Seller holding up small-livestock merchandise at time of sale; 2, Buyer (or spectator) in grandstand; 3, Domestic ducks awaiting sale; 4, Buyers, sellers, &/or spectators lounging; 5, Podium. Ronny Harker, auctioneer, holding mic. &/or gavel; Nancy Stanley, auction clerk; Anthony Sparta, wearing billed cap; 10-14, Sellers displaying small livestock merchandise at time of sale; 15-17, Podium. Ronny Harker, auctioneer Nancy Stanley, clerk; Anthony Sparta, wearing billed cap; 18, White doves awaiting sale; 19-20, Interior panoramas, including podium. Ronny Harker, auctioneer; Nancy Stanley, clerk; Anthony Sparta, wearing billed cap
      - Weekly Saturday night auction, called "the Tabernacle Auction," held at E. H. Harker & Sons auction barn near Tabernacle, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-017; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-017; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Interior of E.H. Harker & Sons' auction barn G-Tabernacle; 25GT, during auction; 1, Spectators and buyers in grandstand; 2, Podium. Ronny Harker, auctioneer; Nancy Stanley, clerk; Anthony Sparta, wearing billed cap, other unnamed individuals; 3, Sellers holding up merchandise at time of sale; 4-8, Interior panoramas during auction; 9, Seller holding up turkey for display at time of sale; 10, Spectators, buyers, &/or sellers lounging at doorway of auction barn; 11-13, Podium. Ronny Harker, auctioneer; clerk; Anthony Sparta, wearing billed cap; Nancy Stanley, other unnamed individuals; 14-15, Mary T. Hufford interviewing unnamed informant; 16-18, Podium. Ronny Harker, auctioneer other unnamed man; 19, Sign advising policies on motor vehicle sales; 20, Buyer making payment at office to Vern Hille, cashier
      - Weekly Saturday night auction, called "the Tabernacle Auction," held at E. H. Harker & Sons auction barn near Tabernacle, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-018; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-018; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Interior of E.H. Harker & Sons' auction barn G-Tabernacle; 25GT, while auction is in progress; 1, Buyers paying Vern Hille, cashier; 2, Interior panorama. On podium is Ronny Harker, auctioneer; Nancy Stanley, auction clerk; Anthony Sparta in blue shirt & billed cap; and other unnamed individuals; 3, Buyers & spectators in grandstand. Christine Cartwright with camera; 4-5, Buyers making purchase at office window; 6-8, Buyers, sellers, & spectators in snack bar; 9-12, Buyers & spectators in grandstand; 13-14, Ronny Harker, auctioneer; 15-18, Ronny Harker, auctioneer; Nancy Stanley, auction clerk; other unnamed man; 19, Seller holding up domesticated duck at time of sale; 20, Ronny Harker, auctioneer
      - Weekly Saturday night auction, called "the Tabernacle Auction," held at E. H. Harker & Sons auction barn near Tabernacle, New Jersey, September 24, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-019; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-019; 14 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-14, Interior of E.H. Harker & Sons' auction barn G-Tabernacle; 25GT while auction is in progress; 1, Ron Harker, auctioneer, on podium, while seller is holding up domesticated duck at time of sale; 2, View from podium of seller holding up goose & at time of sale; 3, Ron Harker, auctioneer on podium; 4-5, View from podium of seller holding up goose at time of sale; 6-7, Ron Harker, auctioneer on podium; 8-11, Seller holding up piglet at time of sale; 12-13, Buyer holding up number during sale; 14, Seller holding up angora rabbit at time of sale
      - Driving around in sourthern Atlantic County, New Jersey, and northern Cape May County, New Jersey; Views of woodlands and sod farm, September 29, 1983 to October 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-020; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-020; 10 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-3, Woods on Cumberland Ave. east of Estell Manor, damaged by gypsy-moth infestation, and partially logged G-Estell Manor; 07GT out; 1-2, Dead trees logged out; 3, Dead trees (killed by gypsy moths) waiting to be logged out; 4-10, Bohm's Sod Farm G-Eldora; 34GT, Eldora; 4, Fertilizer spreader; 5-6, Sod awaiting harvest; 7, Area where sod was recently harvested, awaiting reseeding. Note irrigation pipes left; 8, Sod awaiting harvest; 9-10, Irrigation pump, fuel tank, and sign
      - Visiting docks at Nancy's Harbor on Bidwell Ditch, Middle Township, Cape May County, New Jersey, October 2, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-021; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-021; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Docks G-Nancy's Harbor; 35GT or Bidwell Ditch and boats at Nancy's Harbor, where State Hwy. 47 crosses Bidwell Ditch; 1-2, Ramp Club, small retail business advertising clams, squid, bunker, sheddars, R-C, bait, ice, fish stories, tackle, sodas, cigarettes, candy; 3-5, View of dock; 4-5, Sinks for dressing fish; 6, Wire crab pots; 7- 8, Garvey used for crabbing & gill netting; 9, Gill nets; 10, Fiberglass boat with crab pot; 11-12, View of dock and pilings; 13-15, Garvey used for gill netting; 16, View of dock & pilings; 17-20, Enclosed 25-foot wooden square sterned boat mounted with hydraulically powered reel
      - Driving along roads in Maurice River, Dennis, and Upper Townships, New Jersey, October 2, 1983 to October 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-022; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-022; 10 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Poacher graffiti directed at N.J. Department of Environmental Protection Conservation Officer Herschel Beebe of Eldora; 1-2, Cumberland Co. Hwy. 550, G-Maurice River; 38GT Twp.: "B.B. YOU BETTER RETIRE"; 3, Cumberland Co. Hwy. 548, Maurice River Twp.: "18 DEER WITH OUR DOGS F.U. B.B."; 4-7, Truck gardens in G-Repicivilie; 34GT, seen from Belleplain State Forest fire lookout tower; 8-9, Birdhouse in G-Repicivilte; 34GT; 10, Bill board announcing Festival New Jersey '83, Smithsonian Festival of American Folk life, on State Hwy. 50, Atlantic Co., near G-Corbin City; 04GT
      - Sawing cedar at George Brewer, Jr.'s sawmill, Dennisville, New Jersey, October 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-023; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-023; 15 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-15, George Brewer, Jr. 's cedar sawmill in G-Dennisville; 34GT; 1, Cedar lumber awaiting sale; 2-8, Molder matcher set up for use as a four sided planer; 9-15, Leroy Creamer transporting cedar logs from flatbed truck to sawmmill; 11, Ibid., r., George Brewer, Jr.; 14, Ibid., I., George Brewer, Jr.
      - Sawing cedar at George Brewer, Jr.'s sawmill, in Dennisville, New Jersey, October 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-024; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-024; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Sawing cedar logs into boards at George Brewer Jr. 's sawmll in G-Dennisville; 34GT; 1-3, Looking toward saw from conveyor; 3, L., Leroy Creamer; r., George Brewer, Jr.; 4-6, Sawing boards from a squared off timber; I. Leroy Creamer; r., George Brewer, Jr.; 7-9, Leroy Creamer securing cedar log to carriage of sawmill; 10-13, Leroy Creamer sawing boards from squared off timber; 14-16, Leroy Creamer securing cedar log to carriage of sawmill; 17-18, Leroy Creamer squaring off a log, by sawing off slabs; 19-20, Leroy Creamer sawing boards from squared off timber
      - Sawing cedar log at George Brewer, Jr.'s sawmill in Dennisville, New Jersey, October 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-025; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-025; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, George Brewer, Jr. & Leroy Creamer sawing cedar logs into boards at George Brewer, Jr.'s sawmill in G-Dennisville; 34GT; 1-6, Leroy Creamer trimming a sawn board; 2-6, L., George Brewer, Jr.; r., Leroy Creamer; 7-8, Leroy Creamer securing log on the carriage of the sawmill; I., George Brewer, Jr., r., Leroy Creamer; 9-10, Leroy Creamer squaring a cedar log into a squaredoff timber; 11-18, Leroy Creamer sawing boards off a squared off timber; 18, Pile of cedar logs (rear) awaiting sawmill; 19-20, Leroy Creamer sawing boards off a squared off timber
      - Sawing cedar log into boards at George Brewer, Jr.'s sawmill, Dennisville, New Jersey, October 21, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-026; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-026; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Dennisville; 34GT; 1-18, George Brewer, Jr. & Leroy Creamer sawing boards from cedar logs at George Brewer, Jr. 's sawmill; 1-6, Leroy Creamer sawing boards from squared off timber; 1, Cedar logs (rear) awaiting sawmill; 7-8, Leroy Creamer securing cedar log on carriage of sawmill; 9, Leroy Creamer squaring off cedar log to make a squared off timber; 10, Leroy Creamer securing cedar log on carriage of sawmill; 11-12, Leroy Creamer sawing boards off squared off timber; 11, L., George Brewer, Jr., r., Leroy Creamer; 13-17, Leroy Creamer squaring off a cedar log to make a squared-off timber; 14, Removing slab; 18, Leroy Creamer sawing boards off squared off timber; 19-20, "Flitched" (rough sawn) boards on fork lift awaiting planing, with Leroy Creamer feeding boards iunto molder matcher used as a four-sided planer
      - Sawing boards off cedar log at George Brewer, Jr.'s sawmill, Dennisville, New Jersey, October 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-027; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-027; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Dennisville; 34GT; 1-17, Leroy Creamer feeding "flitched" (rough sawn) boards into the molder matcher, which they use as a four sided planer; 18-19, George Brewer, Jr. and finished lumber; 20, Finished lumber to be loaded & sold (seated, Leroy Creamer; standing, customer).
      - Visit to home of Louis Peterson, Heislerville, New Jersey, October 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-028; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-028; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        G-Heislerville; 38GT; 1-20, Bayman's tools & gear belonging to Louis Peterson; 1-10, Caulking tools; 3-4, Caulking mallets; 5-6, Caulking irons (wad of cotton-like material in upper right center is tow used for caulking); 7-10, "Rocking chair" tool chest for caulking; 11-12, Net reel for hauling gill nets, just built by Louis Peterson; 13, Chain bag of oyster dredge used as a drag anchor; 14-20, Oyster tongs; 14-13, Keyport head; 16-17, Barrel head; 18-19, Wooden head; 20, Louis Peterson holding oyster tongs by their stales (handles)
      - Visit to home of Louis Peterson, Heislerville, New Jersey, October 22, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-029; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-029; 11 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-2, Louis Peterson with oyster tongs outside of his workshop in G-Heislerville; 38GT; 3-4, Interior of Louis Peterson's workshop; 3, Left, net reel; 4, Right, net reel; 5-11, 28-foot garvey, belonging to Louis Peterson.
      - Visit to home of Charlie Pomlear, Belleplain, New Jersey, November 10, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-030; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-030; 13 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-13, Home of Charlie Pomlear, G-Belleplain; 34GT; 1-3, Charlie Pomlear; 4-11, Interior, Pomlear's home; 12-13, Charlie & Myrtle Pomlear's junk hauling truck
      - Salt hay farm, Eldora, New Jersey, November 11, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-031; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-031; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        Salt hay G-Thompson's Beach; 38GT and Eldora; 01-02: Stewart Campbell ll (George's son) stacking b ales of salt hay with forklift and bale farmhand (right); 03-04, Bales of salt hay; 05-06, Black salt hay (Spartina species?) is green growth. "Rosemary" (another Spartina) are tufted shoots; 07, Recently cut meadow of sal hay (proper) (Spartina patens) or "yellow-salt"); 08-09, "Rosemary" salt hay; 10-11, Salt hay (proper) (Spartina radens); 12-14, Bank and ditch for water level control; 15-16, Break in bank caused by muskrat (note shoal of minnows); 18, Same as 12-14; 19-20, Bales of salt hay. Series continues on PFP-83-CJL-043 and 044.
      - Scenes of Bivalve; Maps of Delaware Bay oyster grounds, Bivalve, New Jersey, November 11, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-032; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-032; 18 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-11, Scenes of G-Bivalve; GT; 1-2, Crab pots; 3-5, Oystering docks; 6, Oyster shell bank; 7, Crabbers' live-box; 9-11, Black church: Supreme Council of the House of Jacob of the U.S.A., Inc. G-Bivalve;]; 12-18, Maps of Delaware Bay oystering grounds, at Rutgers University's Shell Fisheries Research Laboratory, G-Bivalve; J.
      - Scenes of Maurice River, near Mauricetown; Robison's Boat Yard, Penny Hill, Mauricetown, New Jersey, November 11, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-033; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-033; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-8, Scenes of G-Maurice River; 38GT, with oyster boats; 1-2, Oyster boats on Maurice River, docked on Maurice River Twp. side, seen from Mauricetown; 3-4, Same as above; with remains of old Maurice River Bridge, Mauricetown; 6-8, Oyster boats on Maurice River, docked on Maurice River Twp. side, seen from new Maurice River Bridge; 9-20, Robison's Boat Yard, G-Penny Hill; 38GT; 9-11, Louis Peterson, bayman of Heislerville, repairing oyster boat "Mary Colman"; 12-16, Louis Peterson's oyster boat, "Mary Colman"; 17-18, Oyster boats on dock, Maurice River, at Robison's Boat Yard, Penny Hill; 19-20, Louis Peterson's oyster boat "Mary Colman."
      - Visit to Robison's Boat Yard, Penny Hill, New Jersey, November 11, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-034; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-034; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Robison's Boat Yard, G-Penny Hill; 38GT; 1, Culling drum on oyster boat; 2-3, Lou Peterson's oyster boat, "Mary Colman," right; 4, Garvey; 5-6, Looking to Maurice River from below the stern of Lou Peterson's oyster boat, "Mary Colman"; 9-10, Sea skiff; 11-14, Clammer's garvey; 15, Oyster boats on blocks; 16-18, Oyster boat, "Amy Carol,"; 19-20, Boat "Fish-N-Fool," modified for oystering.
      - Visit to Robison's Boat Yard, Penny Hill, New Jersey, November 11, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-035; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-035; 8 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-8, Robison's Boat Yard, G-Penny Hill; 38GT; 1, Boat "Fish-N-Fool" modified for oystering; 2, Oyster boats "Mary Jo ll" and "Frances A. Bradford"; 3-8, Oyster boat "Frances A. Bradford."
      - Visit to home of Lynwood R. and Janet Veach, Delmont, New Jersey, November 11, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-036; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-036; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Home of Lynwood R. and Janet Veach, G-Delmont; 38GT; 1-13, Pelts taken by Lynwood R. Veach while trapping; 1-2, Fox pelt; 3-4, Otter pelt; 5-6, Skunk pelt; 7-8, "Pumpkin colored" muskrat pelt; 9-10, Albino muskrat pelts; 11-13, Mounted albino muskrats; 14-15, Mounted wood ducks, shot by Lynwood R. Veach; 16-17, Front: I., Lynwood E. Veach; r.; Janet Veach; rear: I., Lynwood R. Veach; r., Lynwood R. Veach, Jr.; 18-19, List of place names on map of Delaware Bay oyster grounds
      - Opening of small game hunting season, Heislerville Wildlife Management Area, 8 a.m., New Jersey, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-037; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-037; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Pheasant hunters at opening of small game hunting season, G-Heislerville; 38GT Wildlife Management Area, 8 a.m., 11/12/83; 1-7, Pheasant hunters awaiting opening of season, 7:55 a.m.; 8-11, Hunters pheasant hunting; 12-15, N.J. Department of Environmental conservation officer Lynwood E. Veach checking hunting licenses; 16-19, Pheasant hunters hunting; 20, Pheasant hunter with pheasant and retriever
      - Opening of small game hunting season, Heislerville Wildlife Management Area, 8 a.m., New Jersey, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-038; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-038; 7 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-7, Opening of small game hunting season, G-Heislerville; 38GT Wildlife Management Area, 8 a.m., 11/12/83; 1-4, Pheasant hunter with pheasant and retriever; 5-6, N.J. Department of Environmental Conservation officer Lynwood E. Veach; 7, Lynwood E. Veach and granddaughter, Delmont
      - Visit to Lynwood R Veach's eeling dock on West Creek, Eldora, New Jersey, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-039; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-039; 17 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-17, Lynwood R. Veach's eeling dock, on George Campbell's property, West Creek, G-Eldora; 34GT; 1-3, Lynwood R. Veach and Lynwood R. Veach, Jr. on dock; 4-7, Fiberglass eeling boat; 8-10, Lynwood R. Veach raising live box full of eels; 11-14, Live-box; 15-16, Live-box full of eels; 17, Winch on dock
      - Visit to Lynwood R Veach's eeling-equipment shop, Delmont, New Jersey, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-040; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-040; 20 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-20, Lynwood R. Veach's eeling equipment shop at Lynwood E. Veach' s property, G-DeImont; 38GT; 1-10, Eel pots made by Lynwood R. Veach; 11-12, Lynwood R. Veach and eel pots; 13-14, Eel sorting basket; 15, Eel pots made by Lynwood R. Veach; 16, Eel pots and coolers for salt eels; 17-20, Eel pots made by Lynwood R. Veach
      - Visit to eeling-equipment shop of Lynwood R Veach, Delmont, New Jersey, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-041; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-041; 8 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-8, Eeling equipment shop of Lynwood R. Veach, on Lynwood E. Veach's property, G-Delmont; 38GT; 1-4, Barrels of salt eel to be sold for crab bait, in cooler; 5-8, "Skirt" growth on pine tree.
      - Scenes of Bivalve and Shell Pile, Bivalve, New Jersey, November 12, 1983, AFC 1991/023: CJL-042; Jens Lund; PFP-83-CJL-042; 14 color film transparencies (35mm slide)
        1-7, Cedar planks (from George Brewer, Jr. 's sawmill) for oysterboat repair, dock of Bivalve Packing Co., G-Bivalve; J.; 8-14, Oyster schooner "Cashier," supposedly 150 years old, docked on Maurice River, G-Shell Pile; J.